<!-- Copyright 2018 Google Inc.
Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
You may obtain a copy of the License at
    http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0
Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
limitations under the License. -->

<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Developer Stories</string>
    <!-- Break paragraphs without extra spacing, by putting \n at the beginning of next line.-->
    <string name="bio">Hi, my name is Blake.\n\nI love hunting for fish.\n\nScouting for honey holes is my speciality while fishing.\n\nThe knowledge obtained while gathering fish from honey holes is the elemination for the need to, \"fish\" as traditionally implied.\n\nI dream of a never ending catch.\nInstantly hooking my fish, over and over and over again!\n\nFinding honey holes means easy fishing and repeatable, quick catches.\n\nIt is one thing to throw a line in the water with various baits, line types and weights added to the pole hoping to catch something.\n\nIt is a totally different event when you know what you are going out for and know what to look for.\n\nSigns of a Hony Hole include:\n\n- Bubbles\n- Unusually Still Water\n- Wamer Water than Surrounding Saters \n\nMAJOR Signals of a possible hit on a large gathering of fish.\n\nMy biggest catch on a fishing trip happened when I was 11 years old. The final total on the end catch, came in with fish falling out our brown paper grocrey bags, Grandma supplied. \n\n!!Mission complete!!\n\nIn only two hours, my grandfather and I stocked all bags full of Blue Gill. If we had the space we could have even gotten more. \n\nTheir was an easy 75-100 fish from our catch!! \n\nThe Blue Gill were soon filleted into bite size portions of meat. Decidently battered over fat salted butter. Making for an ideal appatizer sized portion of, mouth watering Blue Gill. Skillet frying is the ideal route of speed with this fish. \n\nBlue Gill is more of an odorless fish meaning the flavor of the meat tastes less, \"Fishy\" compared to traditional fish like Salmon.\n\nAll free!!\n\nI learned a little know-how, can go a long way. Especially when given the proper conditions. \n\nCome to find out catching the fish is easy, but only when it\'s biting.\n\n*** Experiencing the success of a big catch on this fishing trip revolutionized the way I look at life and fishing ***\n\nIt was just plain old fishing before. \nNow its the thrill of the hunt + the spoils of your catch!! \n\nI see eating your catch as morally just as long as the food is not being wasted.\n\nFishing in Michigan (when your with me) means, no deep sea gimmics, like trolling and fly fishing is frowned upon. I like to fish in a personal Kayak for added stealth. \n\nPaddle quietly and hover, you will have a better chance finding the honey hole by not scaring the fish off. \n\nSafety in nature is an added bonus for Mid-West fishing (or real estate on the lake). \n\nPositive notable notes off the top of my head (other than the tailgate) while fishing in Michigan include: no aligators, crocidiles or mosquitos w/malaria. \n\nAll you need to worry about when fishing are a few bug bites and a possible sunburn. \n\nIf you have tried fishing before and don\'t like it, I have a bit of advice. Give it one more try and aim for the honey hole fishing spots. After realizing the ease of fishing on a honey hole you will become instantly hooked!\n\nJust as in machine learning we can apply the supervised and unsupervised learning tequniqes into our tackled box of labels. The only diffrence being the approach once labeled not the message. Focusing on 2 pivots, both connected to our bodies senses (or sensor on a phone/IoT Device). These 2 are focused on your vision and tactile feal. Chosen in order to differentiate the type of read you got on the observed fish (saw/felt). \n\nKeeping an eye out for noticeable changes and making mental notes of simple A/B Pivots. \nTo be technically considered an actual \"Natural\" at this sport and others (including argumentative conversations).\nGiven practice, time and setting goals as a commitment to following through to become better are great goals!\n\nI love goals! Espically a goal that revolves around a learnt behavior the individual had learnt from sharing with an assumed trusted confadant in addition to privately witnessing a group like audiatory haluciniziation while alone.\nEfforts to make your personal opinion less effective even while alone (on the legal ramification of stalking and harassment after telling it to leave and getting reacted to all hearing words of relevance) when not getting someone to agree with you as if going to jail alone wasn\'t enough for this police report.  and the group that their natuall talents and the American Freedoms that allow for these talents to be proven unnatural when muddled with.\n\nWhen OUT FISHIN!! I like to create a mental mindscape that isn\'t kept on paper. \n\nOne that is constructed from the personal reaction of a loigcal mind loop (spoken in repetition for the eventual formation of a condensed 1.5 second argument you loose later on an intelligently timed check in). \n\nFinding similarties that stick out in real life allow for simplifying morrally applicaple learnt behaviors through psychology of the Ego while alone in a simingly auditory group environment given trust for what you hear when not seeing it (for example a phone call with no hangup). \nCognitveley use keywords(meta-data) or dog like tags on a fallen solidure and use the aknowledgment of this Behavior as the Therapudic stick you name the label on the change taking place. \n\nOnly we aren\'t pedigreeing regular people into being work horses or \"upgrading\" athleats to juice the bets. \n\nWe are making our lives easier by applying the same logic on a level of productivity that can be proven with increased production. \n\nIn this case years and years of trial and error while traveling and keeping mental note of the physical changes in the environment. \nOr we could take a realisitic approach to the situation and leverage the math with the advantages exploited from an observation. \nMaybe that\'ll be another project but a great UI. Google Forms, connected to sheets, running Python back to the servers rewriting the TFlite pre-trained models to be mass distributed. \n\nThe worst part morrally is possibly the best opportunity to exploit this hack in a real life scenerio of, endangerd species. Personalities are on the line and in danger of unwillingly getting changed over the path of least resistance. True ownership don\'t come with a price it comes with a bill you don\'t gotta legally pay for in America.\n\nIn this scenerio, the noticeable diffrence on hunting given the exposure of animal population desities.\nMaking hunting more like point and click, if you got someone working the scene like an analytical stopwatch mafioso.\n\nOnce in a social setting, just hearing the statement and not responding verbally around others, will make it blame you. J\nust for being honest out loud and admitting to make that responding realize the moral delma.\nOne as being such an invasion on ones privacy even a paid in full, taxed properties isn\'t morally just enough for the legal ramifications of proff and tradition.\n\nJust by talking I am now flip flopping the overlap of others perceived ability to (yes means yes now yes means no logic) try to give you an assumed not implied \"chance\".\n\nThis is an implied chance at getting someone to agree and make ZERO DIFFRENCE ON THE REALITY while trying to change your mental into not just being more upbeat and positive.\nThis must be nice or else attitude comes with a secret rule, NO COMPLAINING EVEN IF YOUR RIGHT.\nThey want you believing the bull and applying it, eventually over a given time span, the eventual desired outcome will most likely happen.\nQuickly on recognition misinterperated aa a, personal fail safe. One initiated by the engagement of failed communication. Reinitiating a memory by making someone say it can make one come to expect. \nLike finishing someones scentence only their is no love family trust or wants from this end. The exposure of perspective to entangle the delusion of paranioa that is knee jerkingly kicked down socially until a flash mob trys to give you the attention to change your world. From your experiences making the effectiveness of your group isolation more benifical to these perpetuating the assumption of a change. \nReal or not on either end leaves opportunities for, acts joked but lied upon to trigger a want for change. \nOnly this time its a natural want recalled from a loss some time after the interaction. \nThe uncomforting momeny causes a memory to be recalled with some loss. The part that actually was uncomforting due to getting disrecpected is quickly forgotten on the memory of the engagement. The only reason I say this as an example is because of something I witnessed while getting coffee. If you mimic ones voice while they are speaking the reverberation of the tone makes the assumption of the voice being the same to the speaker or anyone near by. \nYet given enough physical distance you can see 2 conversations. 1 to make the talker unaware of the manipulation of the integredity of their voice sent for the analysis of a circle back on perspective to make sure one could seamingly keep their job with the delusion in place.\nRe-reving the friction in a reverse order creating a false dependence on a placebo that can only be motivated to promote into actuallity.\n  \nThat female move of desperation while allowing you not to engage in while they talk out the sides of their mouths about you to their friends in their group, exposing their worth as a people from the read.\nFree willing yourself into getting involved with others issues when they pull a personal detail, engage with a friendly rebuttle to add to conversation then..... \nnew phase, learn to say no different and not get guilt tripped into wasting your time with a nobody conversation when you can do it alone just as easy. \n \nA local tip to my grandfather and some dumb luck changed the entire sport for me. This childhood lesson of preparation and timing is an enjoyable memory I didn\'t lazey fair into my life (aka it happened while not being told its what i choose, needed or wanted).\n</string>
    <string name="what_is_your_nickname">What is your Nickname?</string>
    <string name="done">Done</string>
    <string name="team">A-Team</string>
</resources>
